本字幕由 今晚月色真美 個人製作
僅供練習使用  請勿用於商業用途
佛羅倫斯
1476, the dawn of a new era for Italy.
1476年  義大利迎來了新時代的破曉
Arts, culture and science are flourishing under the guidance of inspired minds.
藝術  文化和科學在各種靈感的引導下迅速發展
Renaissance
文藝復興
This is probably the way history will remember us.
這也許就是歷史記錄我們的方式
But in the shadows far from the gold, and the knowledge, lies another truth.
不過  在金錢和知識的陰影下  隱藏著另一個真相
Corruption.
腐敗
Betrayal.
背叛
Murder.
謀殺
Secrets.
秘密
Secrets so dangerous I must hide them.
秘密很危險  我必須將其隱藏
Even from my own family.
即使是我家人  也不能告訴他們
Family, justice, honour,
家庭  正義  榮譽
These are the values guiding my blade.
它們都是引導我刀刃的意義
This truth is written in blood and the shadows are where I strike.
真相以血寫成  我會在陰影籠罩之下發動攻擊
I am Giovanne Auditore.
我叫喬瓦尼·奧迪托雷
And like my ancestors before me.
我和我的先祖們一樣
I am an assassin.
我是一名刺客
刺客信條
血 系
You're coming with me, Avanti.
你跟我來  趕快
洛倫佐·德·美第奇宅邸
I stopped them before Florence.
我在他們到達佛羅倫斯之前阻止了他們
Unfortunately, Your Magnificence, the fourth man escaped.
不幸的是  陛下  第四個人逃走了
What have you heard, Giovanni?
喬瓦尼  你聽到了什麼
Rumors.
傳聞
About an important event that will cause a shift of power.
是關於一個足以改變權力格局的大事件
That man you captured,
你抓到的那個人
Has he spoken yet?
他開口說話了嗎
He will tell us what he knows.
他會把他知道的都一五一十地吐出來
When?
什麼時候
Tell me when!
告訴我什麼時候
In Milano, on the day of Christmas.
在米蘭  聖誕節那一天
The high mass called the priest of Santo Stefano.
大彌撒封賜聖斯特法諾的牧師
米蘭
When?
什麼時候
When the echo of the choir becomes louder at the altar.
當唱詩班在祭壇的回聲越來越大
When the bell rings for the twelfth and last time.
當鐘聲響起第十二次和最後一次
At the altar, the echo of the choir becomes louder.
在祭壇上的唱詩班的回聲越來越大
When the bell rings
當鐘聲響起
For the twelfth and last time.
第十二次和最後一次
The duke of Milano.
米蘭公爵
Will die.
將會死亡
Stop! Stop!
停手  快停手
Don't kill him.
別殺他
Amore...
親愛的…
Ezio's learning fast.
艾吉奧學得很快
It reminds me of you.
讓我想起了你
Ezio, remember, you need to think ahead.
艾吉奧  記住  你必須先人一著
Don't wait for your opponent to move, anticipate and surprise him.
別等你的對手出手  要搶占先機  然後出其不意
How are you, father?
父親  你還好嗎
Good, good.
很好  很好
With the death of the Duke of Milano, Lorenzo de Medici has lost a powerful ally.
米蘭公爵的死  讓洛倫佐·德·美第奇失去了一個強大的盟友
I am sure that his enemies already plot their next move.
我很肯定他的敵人已經策劃了下一步
Sforsa's death was not the end.
斯福爾扎之死不是結束
It was just the beginning.
而是開始
And I know where to fight my next battle.
我知道應該在哪裡繼續我的戰鬥
威尼斯
You served us well in the past.
你過去對我們非常盡責
That is why we are entrusting you to send this letter to our master.
所以我們才委託你把這封信交給我們的主人
It's Perfect. It's just perfect.
完美  簡直完美
After all these years, our time has come, cousin.
這麼多年  我們的時代終於要來了  表哥
Yes.
是啊
You must protect this letter with your life until it is delivered, you understand me?
在這封信成功寄出去之前  你必須以性命來保護這封信  明白嗎
Go to Campus Sant Anzono.
去聖安佐諾大學
Next to the one merchant there's a statue. A man will be waiting for you there.
在一家批發商旁邊有一座雕像  有人在那裡等你
Do not fail us.
不許失敗
What are your masters plotting?
你主人到底在策劃什麼
Speak!
快說
God is my witness, I will cut your throat.
上帝作證  我會割斷你的喉嚨
My life is not yours to take, and my secrets come with me.
我的生命不屬於你  我的秘密將隨我而去
See you in hell.
我們地獄再見
Fool.
蠢貨
佛羅倫斯
Giovanni, did you find anything in Venice?
喬瓦尼  在威尼斯有什麼發現嗎
I intercepted this letter.
我截取到這封密函
Take a look, your Magnificence.
陛下  請過目
It bears the seal of the Barbarigos.
這封密函有巴巴里戈的印章
I never trusted them.
我從不相信他們
Confidantiere.
密碼
An encrypted letter.
一封被加密的密函
It will take several hours to unlock its secrets.
這需要幾個小時來解密
I'll send for you when it's done, Giovanni.
當解密完成了  我會寄給你  喬瓦尼
Get some rest.
去休息吧
Father Maffei.
馬菲神父
You broke the code. That's good.
你成功解密了  非常好
I knew you wouldn't disappoint me, Father Maffei.
我知道你不會令我失望  馬菲神父
Go fetch Giovanni.
去通知喬瓦尼
Tell him he would need to travel shortly.
告訴他  他要外出一段時間
I will wait Lorenzo.
我要等洛倫佐
And Father...
神父…
Remember, you owe us your silence.
記住  你必須保守秘密
Secrets are born here.
秘密在這裡開始
And they die here.
也必須在這裡結束
No one is to know about the content of this letter.
沒有人知道這封密函的內容
Capisci?
明白了嗎
Good, you can go now.
很好  你可以走了
Come back to us soon.
早點回來
I promise.
我答應你
Our son is watching.
咱兒子在看著呢
I know.
我知道
You should talk to him.
你應該和他談談
I will.
我會的
Tell me, papa, why is it that a banker has to leave so often in the middle of the night?
告訴我  父親  為什麼一個銀行家總是要在深夜離開
Business calls, son.
生意上的需要  孩子
Let me come with you.
讓我跟你去
No.
不行
Why not?
為什麼不行
I need you to assist your brother.
我需要你幫助你哥哥
Take care of the family while I'm away.
當我不在家裡時  照顧好家人
I want to help you, father.
我想幫助你  父親
You help me more than you know, Ezio.
你已經幫了我很多了  艾吉奧
More than you know.
比你想像中還要多
Because we broke the seal of the original letter.
因為我們破壞了密函的印章
We had to make an exact copy.
我們必須偽造一個
Father Edmundi is working on one as we speak.
埃穆迪神父正在偽造中
Why?
為什麼
We were unable to decipher it.
我們無法解密
The only way to unlock the secrets of this letter...
只有一個方法能解密這封密函
And find out who masterminded Sforza's assassination...
還有找出策劃刺殺斯福爾扎的幕後黑手
is to deliver it and see where it will lead us.
那就是把信寄出去  它會指引我們
Your Magnificence...
陛下…
I know exactly where in Rome the Barbargos wanted the letter to be delivered.
我知道巴巴里戈要把這封信寄去什麼地方
I can go.
我可以去
Father Maffei, is it ready?
馬菲神父  準備好了嗎
Rome is a dangerous city, my dear Giovanni.
羅馬是一個危險的城市  喬瓦尼
Are you sure you want to carry out this mission without any help?
你確定這個任務你不需要任何幫助嗎
Yes. For the safety of Florence.
是的  為了佛羅倫斯的安全
And the honour of the Medici.
還有為了美第奇的榮譽
So be it.
就這樣吧
Go and find the pit where these snakes hide
去找到毒蛇的老巢
And be merciless.
無需留情
May the father of understanding be with us.
願洞察之父與我們同在
羅馬
Has Rodrigo Borgia become a messenger now?
羅德里戈·波吉亞如今怎麼成送信的了
Not necessary, Your Holiness.
這並不重要  教皇陛下
The death of Duke of Milano changes many things.
米蘭公爵之死改變了很多東西
Is it really?
這是真的嗎
The alliances of men are fragile.
他們的聯盟不堪一擊
Even the city can change hands as easily as money.
城市的統治權甚至可以花錢買來
As long as God is on our side.
只要上帝在我們這一邊
Amen.
阿門
I am told that...
我聽說…
Lorenzo de Medici does not show much respect to our position.
洛倫佐·德·美第奇並不想聽我們的話
That is true. But you can force them to obey you.
確實是  但是您可以逼他們遵從您
Florence is weak now. We should take advantage of it.
佛羅倫斯現在處於弱勢  我們應該從中取利
With your help...
若能得到您的幫助…
It is not part of my office to consent to the death of anyone.
我的職責不是讓人死亡
But my concern is the greater good of Republic of Florence.
而是為了佛羅倫斯共和政體的利益
Therefore I am ready to offer you my spiritual support.
因此我可以給予你精神上的支持
And military help.
還有軍事上的支持
To ensure order is maintained.
以保證秩序不亂
Preserve the honor of the Holy Seal, Rodrigo.
保住神聖印章的榮譽  羅德里戈
You can count on me, Your Holiness.
您可以相信我  陛下
I'm looking for the man who just came in.
我在找剛剛進來的那個人
You must have seen him. Where did he go?
你一定見過他  他去了哪裡
It has been very quiet here today.
今天這裡很安靜
I have seen no other man besides you.
除了你之外  我沒見過其他人
A hood covers his face. He wore black clothes.
他穿黑色衣服  有斗篷遮臉
I cannot help you. Maybe God can.
我幫不了你  也許上帝可以
Pray.
祈禱吧
You will find the answer.
你會找到答案
Your blade won't be enough, assassin.
光靠你的刀刃是不夠的  刺客
What happens now is up to you.
接下來會發生什麼事  取決於你
You have a unique set of skills.
你擁有獨特的技能
Giovanni. That's your name, isn't it?
你叫喬瓦尼  對嗎
A set of skills, I'd be delighted to have on my side.
如果你投靠我這邊  我會非常高興
And what side is that?
你是哪一邊的
The side that is gonna win the war you don't even know it has begun yet.
我會在你發現戰爭發生之前取得勝利
The world is changing under your feet, Giovanni.
你腳下的世界正在發生改變  喬瓦尼
Join us, and you may live to see it.
加入我們吧  你會見證到的
Borgia. Yes, I know your name, too.
波吉亞  我也知道你的名字
I also know how this is going to end.
我也知道這會如何結束
With your fantasy in ruins and an assassin's blade in your throat.
你的幻想將破滅  刺客的刀刃將刺穿你的喉嚨
We shall see.
走著瞧
He's all yours. Get him.
將他拿下
Kill him!
殺了他
That blade almost pierced your heart.
那一刀差點刺穿你的心臟
You haven't spoken a word since you've returned.
自從你回來之後  你沒說過一句話
What's going on, Giovanni?
喬瓦尼  發生什麼事了
Tell me.
告訴我
Sforza's assassination was just the beginning.
刺殺斯福爾扎只是這件事的開端
This is a fast conspiracy, Maria.
這是一個陰謀  瑪麗亞
And I'm pretty sure the next step will occur here, in Florence.
我敢肯定佛羅倫斯會有大事發生
Madonna mia.
我的天啊
In concern for the Medicis' safety.
為了美第奇家族的安全
For the allies faith and for all...
為了聯盟的忠誠  還有這一切…
Papa.
父親
Papa. Father Maffei is here.
父親  馬菲神父來了
He wants you to come with him immediately.
他要你立刻跟他走
He's not alone. Armed men are with him.
他不是一個人來的  還有很多士兵跟著
Calmati, figlio.
冷靜下來  孩子
Why would Lorenzo de Medici would send guards for you?
為什麼洛倫佐·德·美第奇會派守衛找你
Why?
為什麼
I don't know.
我不知道
Go back and tell Maffei I'm already gone.
去告訴馬菲神父我已經走了
Buy me some time.
給我爭取一點時間
Federico. I'm depending on you.
費德里科  我需要你
You're the eldest.
你是長子
Protect the family.
保護你的家人
Go.
去吧
I told you my father isn't here.
我告訴過你了  我父親不在這裡
Out!
出去
And don't ever doubt the word of Auditore again.
以後不要懷疑奧迪托雷家族說的話
Leave this place now.
離開這裡
Calm down.
冷靜下來
Our main problem is that damned assassin.
我們最大的問題是那個該死的刺客
And the investigation threatens our plans.
他調查的東西會威脅到我們的計劃
Don't worry. I'll deal with Giovanni.
別擔心  我會解決掉喬瓦尼
I've already got something in mind.
我已經有辦法了
And then, nothing will stand in our way anymore.
這樣就沒什麼能阻礙我們了
My dear sons...
我親愛的兒子們…
Dark skies are rising over Florence and time is running low.
陰影即將籠罩佛羅倫斯  時間已所剩無幾
The enemy is closer than I thought.
敵人比我想像中還要接近我們
Now, the final battle is about to unfold.
最後一戰即將開始
Every man is mortal and every life comes to an end.
每個人都將戰鬥到最後一刻
But certain things will never change.
但有些東西是永遠不會改變的
Federico and Ezio, my sons...
費德里科  還有艾吉奧  我的孩子們…
Always remember,we are Auditori di Firenze
永遠記住  我們是佛羅倫斯的奧迪托雷家族
And we are assassins.
我們是刺客